SUSEENDHAR LAL

Software Engineer

Hello, I'm a Full Stack Developer with more than 2 years of experience in Web development. I Love Creating High Quality Websites And Apps That Use The Latest And Greatest Tools Out There To Maximize UI And UX Quality. I enjoy the process of making a web site/app from start to finish.



- lssuseendharlal@gmail.com
- Chennai, India
- suseendhar.netlify.app
- github.com/suseendharlal96

- +91-8012543335/+91-7904217073
- 08 August, 1996
- linkedin.com/in/suseendhar-lal-312709155

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer **Object Frontier Software**

03/2020 - Present

Work Order Management

My responsibility:

- I work as Front end developer and I take the responsibility of developing websites from the given UX.
- React along with redux is used for the UI part.
- Analysing the response data and mapping accordingly.

Junior Software Engineer Object Frontier Software

03/2019 - Present Project Mangement System Chennai

Chennai

My responsibility:

- I work as Front end developer using React and also did an important role in creating REST API's using Nodejs.
- Responsible for creating re-usable and flexible components using React and managing store using Redux.

Software Engineer trainee Object Frontier Software

09/2018 - 03/2019

Chennai

Achievements/Tasks

 Got trained as a software engineer and most predominantly on the user interface and frameworks like Reactjs.

SKILLS

NextJs

VueJs/Vuex

VSCode

NoSQL

Headless CMS

PERSONAL PROJECTS

My entire projects portfolio

- All my recent works on various tech stacks
- https://suseendhar.netlify.app/projects

EDUCATION

BE Computer Science Rajalakshmi Engineering College

08/2014 - 04/2018

Chennai

Primary to Higher Secondary TVS Matric School

08/1998 - 03/2014

Madurai

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Limited Working Proficiency

Tamil

Full Professional Proficiency

Sourashtra

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Listening music

Creating mini projects